Haitham Sayed Muhammad

Email: <u>haithamsm95@gmail.com</u> | Mobile: 01002995542 – 01117674980

Marital status: Single Military service : Completed

in in/hiitshaitham 🖸 Haitham95 🙎 https://haitham95.github.io/

Summary:

Started my lifetime self-learning process in 2018 in both programming - As my main field and Digital marketing - As I'm marketing myself now to you, Building friendly user-experience web applications using HTML5 & CSS3, JavaScript, React.js and Git & GitHub for source management, Aligning with the businesses needs and pain points, As my mission is to increase business's value by solving-problems.

Experience:

Social media specialist, InvestWay real estate agency, August 2021 – present

- Building, Designing and maintaining their WordPress website (Website link)
- Managing their social media presence through Facebook and Instagram.
- Increasing return on investment (ROI) through generating leads with paid ads.

Social media specialist trainee, Adcom Egypt marketing agency, July 2021 – August 2021

Managing social media accounts through different social media channels (Facebook – Instagram – LinkedIn)

Telesales representative, Global Housing Corporation, August 2019 – September 2019

- Dealt with American and Canadian businesses to get them interested.
- Building and following up with prospects.

Executive and accountant, Al-Awady International Co. for maintenance of medical devices, May 2017 – May 2018

- Followed up with attendance.
- Dealt with sales and purchases.

Professional Development:

- React The Complete Guide (incl Hooks, React Router, Redux), Udemy, October 2021.
- The complete JavaScript course, Udemy, July 2021.
- Certification in digital marketing advanced track, Udacity (Egypt FWD), May 2021. (View)
- Certification in digital marketing professional track, Udacity (Egypt FWD), Feb 2021. (View)
- Certification in digital marketing challenger track, Egypt FWD (Udcaity), Nov 2020. (View)
- Certification in inbound, HubSpot academy, Jul 2019. (View)
- Design and develop a killer website with HTML5 and CSS3, Udemy, Feb 2019.
- The complete WordPress website business course, Udemy.
- Adobe Photoshop CC essentials training course, Udemy.
- User experience design essentials Adobe XD UI UX design, Udemy.

Education:

- Bachelor of law, English section, Ain-Shams University, 2019
- Graduated from As-Salam Language School, 2014

Skills:

Computer skills:

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript (ES6)
- React (Redux)
- Git & Github

Language skills:

- Arabic: Native.
- English: Good at written and spoken English

- Basic knowledge of Sass, Tailwind and Bootstrap
- Basic knowledge of Photoshop.
- Basic knowledge of Adobe XD & Figma.
- Microsoft Word, Excel & Google Docs.
- WordPress